Guide to the Griffith J. Davis photographs and films, 1946-1991 RL.00292
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Scanned still image negatives, 1946-1949; 342 items 2 boxes
  - Langston Hughes in Atlanta and New York, 1948-1949; 108 items
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-81 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0205)
    - Langston Hughes at Atlanta University with visitors - writer Stetson (?) author of Southern Exposure and freelance photographer Marion Palfi, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-82 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0206)
    - Langston Hughes at Atlanta University with visitors - writer Stetson (?) author of Southern Exposure and freelance photographer Marion Palfi, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-83 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0207)
    - Langston Hughes and Dr. Rufus E. Clement, President of Atlanta University, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-84 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0208)
    - Langston Hughes and Dr. Rufus E. Clement, President of Atlanta University, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-85 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0209)
    - Langston Hughes and Dr. Rufus E. Clement, President of Atlanta University, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-86 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0210)
    - Langston Hughes and Dr. Rufus E. Clement, President of Atlanta University, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-87 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0211)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-88 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0212)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-89 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0213)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-90 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0214)
    - Langston Hughes and Dr. Nathaniel Tillman, Sr., head of Atlanta University English Department, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-91 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0215)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption continues: "Statue of W.E.B. DuBois, former Atlanta University professor."
    - Langston Hughes and Dr. Rufus Clement, President of Atlanta University, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-92 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0216)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-93 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0217)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-94 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0218)
    - Taken at 20 East 127th Street in downstairs living room, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-95 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0219)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption reads "LH-95 et al." The remainder of the caption reads: "Langston Hughes meets with Grace T. Burley of Montpelier, Vermont who regularly corresponded with LH and sent him Vermont maple syrup from time to time. She was also friendly with Era Bell Thompson, seated on right, ("American Daughter"), International Editor of Ebony magazine based in Chicago."
    - Taken at 20 East 127th Street in downstairs living room, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-96 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0220)
    - Taken at 20 East 127th Street in downstairs living room, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-97 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0221)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. Caption reads "LH-95 et al." The remainder of the caption reads: "Langston Hughes meets with Grace T. Burley of Montpelier, Vermont who regularly corresponded with LH and sent him Vermont maple syrup from time to time. She was also friendly with Era Bell Thompson, seated on right, ("American Daughter"), International Editor of Ebony magazine based in Chicago." Griff Davis appears in mirror in this shot.
    - Taken at 20 East 127th Street in downstairs living room, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-98 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0222)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-99 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0223)
      Langston Hughes seated at a table in a dining room with three unidentified women, possibly at Atlanta University.
    - Langston Hughes backstage on Broadway where Canada Lee was playing Lost in the Stars (?), 1949; Original identifier: LH-100 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0224)
      Caption extrapolated by library staff from Griff Davis title list in collection folder. Image not present on contact sheet. Caption continues: "LH-GJD article printed in EBONY." Canada Lee (1907-1952) was a well-known Broadway actor by the 1940s. His costume indicates he was playing the role of George in "Set my people free." The Ebony article (photocopy of first page is located in the Photographs and Papers series) indicates this was his current role at the time the article was written.
    - Langston Hughes backstage on Broadway where Canada Lee was playing Lost in the Stars (?), 1949; Original identifier: LH-101 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0225)
      Caption transcribed by library staff from Griff Davis title list in collection folder. Image not present on contact sheet. Caption continues: "LH-GJD article printed in EBONY." Canada Lee (1907-1952) was a well-known Broadway actor by the 1940s. His costume indicates he was playing the role of George in "Set my people free." The Ebony article (photocopy of first page in the collection folder) indicates this was his current play.
    - Nate White, secretary to Langston Hughes in 1948-50 period in NYC, 1948-1951; Original identifier: LH-102 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0226)
      Title transcribed from Griff Davis title list in collection. White is shown with Langston Hughes.
    - Nate White, secretary to Langston Hughes in 1948-50 period in NYC, 1948-1951; Original identifier: LH-103 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0227)
    - Nate White, secretary to Langston Hughes in 1948-50 period in NYC, 1948-1951; Original identifier: LH-104 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0228)
    - Nate White, secretary to Langston Hughes in 1948-50 period in NYC, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-105 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0229)
    - No known title, circa 1950; Original identifier: LH-106 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0230)
    - Langston Hughes backstage with Nellie Lutcher (?) in New York City, 1949; Original identifier: LH-107 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0231)
    - Langston Hughes backstage with Nellie Lutcher (?) in New York City, 1949; Original identifier: LH-108 (Box 3, Image RL.00292-N-0232)
      Caption extrapolated by library staff from Griff Davis title for LH-107 image. Caption continues: "Printed in EBONY 'backstage' article." Nellie Lutcher (1912-2007) was a jazz and R&B singer and pianist.
  - Hale Woodruff and Charles Alston in the studio, 1948-1949; 110 items
    Charles Alston and Hale Woodruff were 20th century African American artists. Although they were known for their commissioned mural works, they also created paintings, sculptures, and other artworks.
    In the late 1940s Alston and Woodruff began work on a mural project commissioned by Golden State Mutual Life Insurance Company, which asked the artists to illustrate African American contributions to the settling of California. Alston worked with Woodruff on the murals in a large studio space in New York; they used ladders to reach the upper parts of the canvas. The mural consists of two panels: "Exploration and Colonization" by Alston and "Settlement and Development" by Woodruff. The murals were unveiled in 1949 at the Golden State Mutual Headquarters in Los Angeles.
    [Source: adapted from Wikipedia page on Charles Alston, viewed July 1, 2021]
    The images in this group, in safety film negative format, were taken by photojournalist Griff Davis in the late 1940s to document African American artists Charles Alston and Hale Woodruff as they worked in their New York City studio on a mural project for the Golden State Mutual Life Insurance Company. The giant mural was commissioned by the Los Angeles-based African American-owned company to illustrate the historic role of African Americans in the settling of California. These studio photos feature the artists at work; other people - unidentified sitters and casual visitors - also appear in the photographs. There are also a handful of color images of some of Charles Alston's modernist paintings and one sculpture.
    Positive digital scans of these negatives are available for viewing through the links in each entry.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA1 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0233)
      Hale Woodruff and Charles Alston.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA2 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0234)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA3 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0235)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA4 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0236)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA5 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0237)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA6 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0238)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA7 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0239)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA8 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0240)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA9 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0241)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA10 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0242)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA11 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0243)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA12 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0244)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA13 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0245)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA14 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0246)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA15 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0247)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA16 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0248)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA17 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0249)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA18 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0250)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA19 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0251)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA20 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0252)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA21 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0253)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA22 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0254)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA23 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0255)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA24 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0256)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA25 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0257)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA26 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0258)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA27 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0259)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA28 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0260)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA29 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0261)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA30 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0262)
      Hale Woodruff.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA31 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0263)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA32 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0264)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA33 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0265)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA35 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0266)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA36 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0267)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA37 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0268)
      Someone seen only from shoes, looking at photographs on the floor.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA38 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0269)
      View of a panel.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA39 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0270)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA40 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0271)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA41 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0272)
      Charles Alston.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA42 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0273)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA43 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0274)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA44 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0275)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA45 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0276)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA46 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0277)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA47 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0278)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA48 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0279)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA49 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0280)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA50 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0281)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA51 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0282)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA52 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0283)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA53 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0284)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA54 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0285)
      Hale Woodruff (?), foreground, and unidentified sitter.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA55 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0286)
      Hale Woodruff, Charles Alston, and unidentified man.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA56 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0287)
      Hale Woodruff and unidentified sitter.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA57 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0288)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA58 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0289)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA59 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0290)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA61 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0291)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA62 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0292)
      Hale Woodruff and unidentified man.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA63 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0293)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA64 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0294)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA65 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0295)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA66 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0296)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA67 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0297)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA68 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0298)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA69 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0299)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA70 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0300)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA71 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0301)
      Charles Alston with unidentified young man.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA72 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0302)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA73 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0303)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA74 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0304)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA75 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0305)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA76 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0306)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA77 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0307)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA78 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0308)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA79 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0309)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA80 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0310)
      Hale Woodruff with unidentified man.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA81 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0311)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA82 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0312)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA83 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0313)
      Charles Alston with unidentified young man and little girl.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA84 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0314)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA85 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0315)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA86 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0316)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA87 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0317)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA88 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0318)
      View of a panel. Contact sheet labeled "Sheet M".
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA89 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0319)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA90 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0320)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA91 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0321)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA92 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0322)
      View of a panel. Contact sheet labeled "Sheet N".
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: Alston Panel 1 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0323)
      Shows part of panel. Color positive transparency. Image not present on contact sheet.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: Alston Panel 2 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0324)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: Alston Panel 3 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0325)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: Alston Panel 4 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0326)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: Woodruff Panel 5 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0327)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA 30, 31, 32 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0328)
      Contact sheet labeled "Sheet O". 35mm strips. Numbers represent frames.
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA 33, 34, 35 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0329)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: HW/CA 36, 37 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0330)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 1 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0331)
      This series of images of modernist paintings and one sculpture by Alston (labeled Alston 1-12) are accompanied by a variety of notes, one in Davis' hand. The latter reads, "Perhaps related to big spread Fortune [magazine] did on Jacob Lawrence paintings (about 63?). Lawrence was Alston's protégé. Griff Davis, 9/23/87." And from a photocopied slip, "Charles Alston Paintings taken in 1949 prob in NYC." "For Life"; an archivist's note on the slip reads "Front of envelope that contained photos of Alston paintings."
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 2 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0332)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 3 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0333)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 4 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0334)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 5 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0335)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 6 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0336)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 7 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0337)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 8 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0338)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 9 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0339)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 10 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0340)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 11 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0341)
    - No known title, 1948; Original identifier: C. Alston 12 (Box 2, Image RL.00292-N-0342)
- Films by Griff Davis, 1952-1957
  Access note. Collection contains fragile materials. Original 16mm prints in the Griffith Davis collection are closed to use, but have been digitized. To request access to the digital files made from the films, click the "Request for Onsite Use" button then select "RL00292-SET-0001."
  - Pepperbird Land - Liberia, 1952; 0:23:11, color, sound (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0001, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
    Can label: "Filmed for the Republic of Liberia by Griffith J. Davis for distribution to all its Embassies and Consulates Abroad." Produced by Griffith J. Davis. Narrated by Sidney Poitier. The documentary film was commissioned by President William V. S. Tubman.
  - Visit of the Gold Coast Prime Minister Kwame Nkrumah to Liberia and his interest in Point 4 Projects, 1953-01; 0:06:26, bw, sound (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0002, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
    Can label: "Used in USIA Africa Regional Newsreel; Filmed by Griffith J. Davis; U.S.I.S. Film." United States Information Service production.
  - Coke Tales for Dorothy, Monrovia Children's Birthday Party, part A, 1956; 0:12:44, bw, silent (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0003, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
    A birthday party for 3-year-old Dorothy Davis, daughter of Griffith Davis, in Monrovia, Liberia. Griffith Davis's wife, Muriel Corrin Davis, and their infant son, Benjamin, also appear throughout the film. Some footage repeats in RL00292-F16-0004.
  - Coke Tales for Dorothy, Monrovia Children's Birthday Party, part B, 1956; 0:14:01, bw, silent (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0004, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
    A birthday party for 3-year-old Dorothy Davis, daughter of Griffith Davis, in Monrovia, Liberia. Griffith Davis's wife, Muriel Corrin Davis, and their infant son, Benjamin, also appear throughout the film. Some footage repeats in RL00292-F16-0003.
  - Liberia - 1956 Presidential inauguration of William V.S. Tubman and William R. Tolbert, 0:59:54, bw, sound (Film-reel Film master: Reel 1, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0005, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
    A Bureau of Information Film, produced by Beauford A. Mensah assisted by Griffith J. Davis.
  - The President and the Press Exhibition on the 10th Anniversary of the Liberian Age Newspaper, 1956-05; 0:11:28, bw, silent (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0006, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
    Silent footage of people visiting the exhibit, including William V.S. Tubman and William Tolbert.
  - Liberia - Night Village - Dancing, unedited part A, filmed by Griffith J. Davis, 1956; 0:17:17, bw, silent (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0007, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
    Silent footage of Liberian dancing devils and other dance troupes.
  - Liberia - Night Village - Dancing, unedited part B, filmed by Griffith J. Davis, 1956; 0:20:04, bw, silent (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0008, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
  - Progress Through Cooperation: The Story of Liberia's Agricultural Program, part 1, 1957; 0:31:55, color, sound (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0009, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
    Presented by the Joint Liberian-United States Commission for Economic Development and the Department of Agriculture and Commerce, filmed and edited by Griffith J. Davis. Produced by the Audio Visual Center, technical assistance by the International Cooperation Administration and the U.S. Department of Agriculture.
  - Progress Through Cooperation: The Story of Liberia's Agricultural Program, part 2, 1957; 0:32:07, color, sound (Box 7, Film-reel RL00292-F16-0010, Digital-materials RL00292-SET-0001)
  - Legacy videocassette and DVD use copies of films, 1952-1957 (Box 4, Box 5)
    These copies of the films were created specifically for user access, and are superseded by the high resolution digital scans now available in RL00292-SET-0001.